



# ALEJANDRO MARTÍN

3D CHARACTER ANIMATOR

- alehamartinva@gmail.com
- +34 671 213 938
- https://alehaaaa.github.io/
- Berlin, Germany Barcelona, Spain

PROFILE

I am a 3D character animator with intuition and an eye for detail. Experienced in production environments, receiving feedback from the Animation Director and Supervisor and collaborating with other Animators and the Rigging team, always pursuing a more efficient pipeline with custom scripts and tools.

I am excited to join a team-working production and start animating!

# EDUCATION

#### MASTER IN 3D CHARACTER ANIMATION

ECIB | 2021 - 2022

Lip-sync · Advanced Acting

#### **DEGREE IN ANIMATION**

ECIB | 2019 - 2021

 $2D \cdot StopMotion \cdot 3D$ 

### ACTING INTRODUCTION EÒLIA THEATER SCHOOL 2021 - 2022

#### TOOLS

M AUTODESK MAYA

**U** ANIMBOT

🏖 PYTHON

SHOTGRID

#### LANGUAGES

English (Fluent)
Spanish (Native)
Catalan (Native)

# EXPERIENCE

# JUNIOR/MID 3D ANIMATOR - DIE SCHULE DER MAGISCHEN TIERE 4 LUMATIC (BERLIN, GERMANY) | NOV 2024 - CURRENTLY

Researched and explored a more stylized animation look through a new character. Continued to collaborate with the Supervisor and Director.

# JUNIOR 3D ANIMATOR - DIE SCHULE DER MAGISCHEN TIERE 3 LUMATIC (BERLIN, GERMANY) | NOV 2023 - JUN 2024

Maintaining the deadlines, I worked on a wide range of sequences problem-solving and finding the comedic timing.

- Animated a variety of animal characters with lip-syncs, studying references and learning from their anatomical behaviours.
- Received feedback directly from the Animation Director.
- Team-worked to push sequences to their best acting potential.
- Improved the animation pipeline creating custom tools and scripts.

# 3D CHARACTER ANIMATOR FOR SHORT FILM - EL MEGA ROBO ECIB (CINEMA SCHOOL OF BARCELONA) | OCT 2022 - SEP 2023

Collaboration with the Director and other animators, I realized ideas and constructed the story from beginning to end.

- Developed and animated the characters giving them personalities and learning to highlight the subtle details of their performances.
- Worked on a pose Library and test animations.